So, for the first improvement by me is add this (picture slider)
and change the background.
So, the background by me is show the logo of the "Mi Ayam".
And, maybe add that one (background) so the points and message can be clearly seen, like that.
Okay, the next maybe the concept is same with this,
add "Delete Account" in the setting page.
Maybe not too far different with this because
from me it's just like adding (an improvement), like that.
And also adjusted with the design.
And also adjusted with the design. / Yes.
Then, for the "Edit Profile", delete (input field) instagram and facebook, right?
Yes.
Yes, instagram and facebook. So the display is full one page and no need to scrolling down. Like that.
So it's straight from e-mail, name, (phone) number, birth date, straight to delivery address. Like that.
And then, for the detail menu, because the text on the previous design is over to "add" button, it's changed like this so it's not over (to "add" button). Like that.
Maybe this is will be a bit same with the second design, because the focus is to improve or to revise an over sentences. Like that.
Okay. / Okay.
Nah, for the design by me
the first is the picture on the top maybe can be changed, so the points and the message are more clearly.
The previous design is too disguised.
And then, add the picture slider to this, so the pictures are automatic slide, without the user slide the pictures manually.
Nah, for the navigation itself, if the "plus" sign is clicked, then the display like this will appear.
Nah, if (the user) wants to (order) delivery (and click delivery button), then "menu restoran" page will appear.
Nah, from the "menu restoran" page, an improvement is maybe on the description. The description is arrange neatly, so the description didn't collide with "add" button.
So it's neatly in this version.
Nah, then, from the menu "account" is also add "delete account"
same as the first design
so the users can delete their account.
The different from Izzat's design is in icon.
Yes, the different is in the icon.
Yes, that's right.
Then, in "Edit Profile" part, it's the same (with design 1), delete  (input field) instagram and facebook
so, maybe it can be simpler.
[There are 5 people that participated on design voting: Diyah, Nila, Annisa, Mia, and Alliya]
Assalamualaikum Warrahmatullahi Wabarakatuh
Here I will do evaluation for the design that have been presented.
The first is I will talk over the background in "Home" menu.
So, according to me, the first design already has a nice background
because it has a logo in the middle, so it looks better and more attractive if compared with the second design
because the background in the second design is only solid color background, so it seems less attractive.
Then, the second that I will discuss is the carousel where also located in the "Home" page.
According to me, the carousel in the first design is less attractive
because the circles is too close to the promo above and the promo below, so it seems less attractive.
Nah, for the second design, according to me, the circles is better and more attractive because there are colors in the circles too.
Then the third is the "Menu" part.
According to me, the "Menu" part in the first design is better, because the reason is in menu detail.
According to me, menu detail from the first design is more clearly and more detail because it also desribe the flavours
meanwhile in the second design, in my opinion, an explanation is less obvious
and didn't reflect the menu.
Then the fourth, in "Account" part, exactly in "Delete Account" part.
According to me, the part of "Delete Account" in both first design and the second design is nice
because for the first design, I like the "Delete Account" icon
because the "Delete Account" icon in the first design is more common if compared to the second design
because commonly, delete icon that has been a lot or common in the application or web is the form of garbage.
But, I also like the "Account" design of the second design because the second design gives more space, so its more pleasant to be seen by user
and seems more clearly.
Then the last that I'll discuss is an "Edit Profile" part.
According to me, an "Edit Profile" part in the second design is better
because, for the "delivery address" part, in the first design is too close with the "birth date" part
so, it seems less good for the user too.
A whole of both the design, according to me is already nice. But if I was asked to choose, I choose the first design.
Before voting, allow me to give a sight about plus and minus of the first design and the second design.
For the first design, the minus is an inconsistent font when add "Delete Account" feature.
The font should be the same with the other font. Or if want to change the font, then change all of it.
Then, for the points and message icon that located in "Home" page
its visible that the stroke and border of the icon are thin whereas the original design is already good
but what I like in the first design is when you put the logo on the top middle of "Home" page, it's really nice for branding.
Move to the second design, the plus of the second design is when click plus button, there will appear delivery and reserve button.
Then, the automatic slider part is good too.
Then in "Menu" revision part between both design are almost resemble, right?
So, at the end, going to more like or will vote the second design.
So, I choose the second design because the design is more concise.
Then, I like the design of the voucher, it's unique.
And in the menu, it's described completely.
I'm Mia Amelia, I want to give my sight for both of the design.
According to me, I more like the second design
because there are some features like: the pictures can be slide automatically
so user don't have to slide manually
and there's navigation button, in my opinion it's more attractive.
Then, the background in the top middle can be replaced
so I more like and vote the second design.
So, I ask permission to opine plus and minus from each design.
For the first design, I like it because
there's a logo, so the "Home" page is not too lonely
and its clarify that this application indeed belong to Mi Ayam Jamur Haji Mahmud.
Then, the minus is on a slide part, the slide icon is less contrast with the background
So sometimes, I'm as a user of other application doesn't know that it can be slide.
Then for the points icon, for me it's a bit less attractive because
the shape is less attractive, because it's too Microsoft Word's shape.
And then, in "My Account" part, the fonts is different and don't same, so it less pleasant to seen.
Then, in "Edit Profile" page, in "delivery address" part, the font is different.
And according to me, it's too high, eh, too close with birth date.
For the second design, I like because the font is same (consistent) and already neat.
Then, seems like the "My Order" font is less to the right.
Then also
the color of the slides, the orange circles are already contrast with the background, so although the feature already automatic slide
but it's like, we know that we can slide manually.
Then I also like the navigation, so it's like, give us choice directly whether we want to delivery or reserve.
Maybe the red one, for me it's too dark, so it can be enchance.
Then, the minus of the second design is the part of "Home" page on the top, is a bit lonely
so, it like less contains. So it can be added by logo.
So, that's all.
Then if I was asked to choose from both of those design, I prefer the second design.
Thank you.